Indiana University President's Office records, 1937-1962 C213
Indiana University Archives
- Subject files, 1937-1962
  - Division of University Extension (Box 192)
    - Indianapolis, 1957-1958 (Box 192)
    - Kokomo, 1957-1958 (Box 192)
    - South Bend, 1957-1958 (Box 192)
    - Southeastern, 1957-1958 (Box 192)
    - All Centers – General, 1958-1959 (Box 192)
    - All Centers – Enrollment Summaries, 1958-1959 (Box 192)
    - Annual Report, 1958-1959 (Box 192)
    - Audio Visual Center – General, 1958-1959 (Box 192)
    - Audio Visual Center – Net Film Service, 1958-1959 (Box 192)
    - Bloomington, 1958-1959 (Box 192)
    - Bureau of Studies in Adult Education, 1958-1959 (Box 192)
    - Calumet Center, 1958-1959 (Box 192)
    - Comparative Bookstore Balance Sheets, 1958-1959 (Box 192)
    - Comparative General Financial Report, 1958-1959 (Box 192)
    - Dean of Faculties File, 1958-1959 (Box 192)
    - Fort Wayne, 1958-1959 (Box 192)
    - Gary, 1958-1959 (Box 192)
    - Kokomo, 1958-1959 (Box 192)
    - South Bend, 1958-1959 (Box 192)
    - Southeastern, 1958-1959 (Box 192)
    - Annual Report, 1959-1960 (Box 192)
    - Audio Visual Center – General, 1959-1960 (Box 192)
    - Audio Visual Center – Net Film Service, 1959-1960 (Box 192)
    - Bloomington, 1959-1960 (Box 192)
    - Bureau of Studies in Adult Education, 1959-1960 (Box 192)
    - Fort Wayne, 1959-1960 (Box 192)
    - Gary - General, 1959-1960 (Box 192)
    - Gary - Dedication, 1959-1960 (Box 192)
    - Kokomo, 1959-1960 (Box 192)
    - South Bend, 1959-1960 (Box 192)
    - Southeastern, 1959-1960 (Box 192)
    - Audio Visual Center – General, 1960-1961 (Box 192)
    - Audio Visual Center – Net Film Service, 1960-1961 (Box 192)
    - Bloomington, 1960-1961 (Box 192)
    - Bureau of Studies in Adult Education, 1960-1961 (Box 192)
    - Calumet Center, 1960-1961 (Box 192)
    - Fort Wayne, 1960-1961 (Box 192)
    - Kokomo, 1960-1961 (Box 192)
  - Division of University Extension, 1960-1962; (24 folders) (Box 193)
  - Extra Sections, 1937-1940; (3 folders) (Box 193)
  - Eyster, Elvin S., 1941-1945; (4 folders) (Box 193)
  - F, 1937-1962; (26 folders) (Box 193)
  - Faculty, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 194)
    - And Administration, 1937 (Box 194)
    - Age Distribution, 1940-1941 (Box 194)
    - Annual Reports, 1947-1962; (12 folders) (Box 194)
    - Appointments, 1946-1952; (12 folders) (Box 194)
    - Associates, 1961-1962 (Box 194)
  - Faculty-Faculty available as consultants to Business and Industrial Firms, 1961-1962 (Box 194)
    - Award for Good Teaching, 1946-1948; (2 folders) (Box 194)
    - Bibliographies, 1939-1951; (9 folders) (Box 194)
    - Bonus, 1941-1942 (Box 194)
    - Booklet, Faculty Constitution, etc., 1947-1953; (6 folders) (Box 194)
    - Club (Mens), 1945-1956; (11 folders) (Box 194)
  - Faculty-Club (Mens), 1956-1962; (6 folders) (Box 195)
    - Council, 1947-1962; (43 folders) (Box 195)
      - Agenda, 1952-1962; (6 folders) (Box 195)
      - Committees, 1949-1962; (13 folders) (Box 195)
    - Council, 1952-1959; (13 folders) (Box 195)
  - Faculty Council, 1949-1950; (6 folders) (Box 196)
  - Feinberg Committee (Box 196)
  - Faculty Council, (2 folders) (Box 196)
  - Committee to Nominate Candidates for Secretary of Faculty Council (Box 196)
  - Faculty Council, (17 folders) (Box 196)
    - Minutes, 1947-1953; (5 folders) (Box 196)
  - Faculty Council, 1952-1959; (2 folders) (Box 196)
    - Minutes, 1959-1960 (Box 196)
  - Faculty-Data, 1948-1949; (2 folders) (Box 196)
    - Discussion Club, 1949-1962; (14 folders) (Box 196)
    - Election Committee, 1947-1962; (16 folders) (Box 196)
    - Emeritus and Retired Faculty Administrative Officers, 1940-1962; (21 folders) (Box 196)
    - Fee Courtesy, 1939-1940 (Box 196)
    - Form Letters Sent to Faculty, 1938-1944; (6 folders) (Box 196)
  - Faculty-Form Letters, 1944-1962; (18 folders) (Box 197)
    - Handbook, 1946-1962; (12 folders) (Box 197)
    - Histories, 1945-1959; (2 folders) (Box 197)
    - Honors, 1945-1954; (6 folders) (Box 197)
    - Leaves of Absence, 1943-1962; (19 folders) (Box 197)
    - Lists, 1938-1940; (2 folders) (Box 197)
    - Of I.U. who will retire within the next five years, 1940-1941 (Box 197)
    - List, Miscellaneous, 1947-1948 (Box 197)
    - Lists, New Members, 1940-1946; (6 folders) (Box 197)
  - Faculty-Lists, New Members, 1946-1962; (17 folders) (Box 198)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1939-1942; (4 folders) (Box 198)
    - Memos, 1937-1938 (Box 198)
    - Necrology, 1951-1968; (14 folders) (Box 198)
    - New Faculty, 1939-1960; (4 folders) (Box 198)
    - Newsletter, 1952-1957; (5 folders) (Box 198)
  - Faculty-Newsletters, 1957-1962; (6 folders) (Box 199)
    - Notices, 1947-1950; (2 folders) (Box 199)
    - Data, 1948-1949 (Box 199)
    - Notices, 1949-1951; (2 folders) (Box 199)
    - Offered Positions Elsewhere, 1948-1952; (4 folders) (Box 199)
    - Outside Faculty Activities and Extra Compensation Policy, 1960-1962; (2 folders) (Box 199)
    - Physical Examination, 1942-1962; (18 folders) (Box 199)
    - Policies, 1940-1941 (Box 199)
    - Positions, 1937-1941; (2 folders) (Box 199)
    - Promotions, 1941-1946; (6 folders) (Box 199)
  - Faculty-Promotions, 1945-1962; (48 folders) (Box 200)
    - Prospects, 1941-1942 (Box 200)
    - Publications File, 1938-1949; (3 folders) (Box 200)
  - Faculty-Publications, 1955-1961; (6 folders) (Box 201)
    - Questionnaire to Those Here 20 Years on Student Ability Now and 20 Years Ago, 1939-1940 (Box 201)
    - Rating, 1945-1953; (9 folders) (Box 201)
    - Reappointments, 1945-1962; (23 folders) (Box 201)
    - Regarding Retirement of Members of Faculty, 1937-1938 (Box 201)
    - Replacements, 1938-1942 (Box 201)
    - Of I.U. Who will Retire, 1941-1942 (Box 201)
    - Retirement, 1943-1962; (20 folders) (Box 201)
    - Returned from Leave-Letters of Welcome, 1945-1946 (Box 201)
    - Rules and Regulations-Other Schools, 1949-1959 (Box 201)
    - Salaries, 1943-1955; (18 folders) (Box 201)
  - Faculty-Salaries, 1955-1962; (7 folders) (Box 202)
    - Speech, 1947-1957; (5 folders) (Box 202)
    - Statistics, 1946-1947 (Box 202)
    - Subversive Teaching Report - "Investigation held at Indiana University, Bloomington, Indiana", December 3 and 4, 1946 (Box 202)
      - (Folder 1) (Box 202)
      - (Folder 2) (Box 202)
      - (Folder 3) (Box 202)
    - Suggestions, 1948-1953; (2 folders) (Box 202)
    - Tenure, 1940-1946; (6 folders) (Box 202)
  - Temporary Appointments, 1946-1947 (Box 202)
  - Faculty-Tenure, 1946-1953; (12 folders) (Box 202)
    - Title Changes, 1943-1944 (Box 202)
    - War Service, 1946-1947 (Box 202)
    - Women's Club, 1949-1962; (12 folders) (Box 202)
  - Fal, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 202)
  - Fall Semester-Opening Delayed-Housing Shortage, 1946-1947 (Box 202)
  - Fal, 1948-1955; (6 folders) (Box 202)
  - Falk, Charles J. (Box 202)
  - Falwell, Georgia M., 1945-1946 (Box 202)
  - Fam, 1941-1962; (20 folders) (Box 202)
  - Far, 1937-1955; (13 folders) (Box 202)
  - Far Eastern Student Emergency Fund, 1937-1938 (Box 202)
  - Farwell, Dr. Olivia A. Hers Collection, 1939-1940 (Box 202)
  - Fas, 1937-1962; (24 folders) (Box 202)
  - Fe, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 203)
  - Federal-Miscellaneous, 1941-1942 (Box 203)
  - Federal Aid to Defray Cost of Accelerated War Program, 1941-1942 (Box 203)
  - Federal Aid to Education, 1948-1961; (13 folders) (Box 203)
  - Federal Home Loan Bank (Box 203)
  - Federal Housing Administration Underwriting Division-Training Program, 1938-1939 (Box 203)
  - Federal Surplus Food Commodities Use of by Students at I.U., 1939-1942; (3 folders) (Box 203)
  - Federal Works Agency, 1945-1948; (3 folders) (Box 203)
  - Fees-Rulings and Copies of Minutes, 1938-1939 (Box 203)
  - Fees, 1936-1962; (35 folders) (Box 204)
  - Fel, 1937-1955; (12 folders) (Box 204)
  - Fellowships, 1939-1951; (18 folders) (Box 204)
  - Fellowships, 1951-1962; (14 folders) (Box 205)
  - Feltus, Paul L., 1937-1947; (10 folders) (Box 205)
  - Fen, 1941-1962; (21 folders) (Box 205)
  - Fenneman, Fred W., 1938-1939 (Box 205)
  - Fer, 1937-1955; (7 folders) (Box 205)
  - Ferguson, 1947-1948 (Box 205)
  - Ferguson, Jesse D., 1938-1941 (Box 205)
  - Fertsch, Albert, 1938-1954 (Box 205)
  - Quotations-Lawyers Sonnet written by Thomas Hornsby Ferrill (Box 205)
  - Fesler, James WM., 1939-1947; (2 folders) (Box 205)
  - Fi, 1937-1957; (20 folders) (Box 205)
  - Fi, 1957-1962; (5 folders) (Box 206)
  - Fidelity and Casuality Company of New York, 1937-1954; (17 folders) (Box 206)
  - Field, Alice Grunfeld, 1944-1946; 1 Folder (Box 206)
  - Field, Oliver P., 1940-1954; (14 folders) (Box 206)
  - Field Station (Anthropology), 1955-1956 (Box 206)
  - Fielder's Addition Lots Purchase, 1939-1940 (Box 206)
  - Field House Callable Bonds, 1937-1938 (Box 206)
  - Film Council of America, 1947-1953; (7 folders) (Box 206)
  - Films of I.U., 1949-1951; (2 folders) (Box 206)
  - Fin, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 207)
  - Finance, I.U., 1939-1941; (3 folders) (Box 207)
  - Financial Counselor Advisors, 1937-1938 (Box 207)
    - Statistics, 1939-1940 (Box 207)
  - Financing-Hospitals and Colleges, 1939-1940 (Box 207)
  - Financial-Reports Acknowledgements, 1940-1941 (Box 207)
    - Statistics, 1940-1941 (Box 207)
  - Financing-Hospitals and Colleges, 1940-1941 (Box 207)
  - Financial-Reports Acknowledgements, 1941-1942 (Box 207)
    - Statistics, 1941-1942 (Box 207)
  - First National Bank, Bloomington, 1941-1942 (Box 207)
  - Financial Report, 1944-1945 (Box 207)
    - Statement, 1944-1945 (Box 207)
  - Financial Report, 1945-1946 (Box 207)
    - Statement, 1945-1946 (Box 207)
  - Financial Report, 1946-1947 (Box 207)
    - Statement, 1946-1947 (Box 207)
  - Financial Report, 1947-1948; (2 folders) (Box 207)
    - Statement, 1947-1948 (Box 207)
  - Financial Report, 1948-1949 (Box 207)
    - Statement, 1948-1949 (Box 207)
  - Financial Report, 1949-1962; (13 folders) (Box 207)
  - Fine Arts (Box 207)
    - 1937-1943 (Box 207)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 207)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 207)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 207)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 207)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 207)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 207)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 207)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 207)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 207)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 207)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 207)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 207)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 207)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 207)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 207)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 207)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 207)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 207)
      Includes a reprint of Jack Wasserman's "S. Marta al Vaticano" from Capitolium (No. 9, 1961)
  - Fine Arts Building, 1959-1962 (Box 207)
  - Finer, Herman, 1940-1941 (Box 207)
  - Finley, Georgia E., 1937-1939; (2 folders) (Box 207)
  - Finn, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 207)
  - Fire (Box 207)
  - First Methodist Church, 1938-1960; (2 folders) (Box 207)
  - First National Bank, Bloomington, 1938-1945; (7 folders) (Box 207)
  - First National Bank, Bloomington, 1945-1962; (17 folders) (Box 208)
  - Fis, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 208)
  - Fischer, Karl W., 1937 (Box 208)
  - Fisher, L.L., 1938-1953; (15 folders) (Box 208)
  - Fit, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 208)
  - Fitzgerald, Dean L.E. (Box 208)
  - Fl, 1937-1946; (9 folders) (Box 208)
  - Fl, 1946-1962; (16 folders) (Box 209)
  - Flag at Half Mast, 1939-1940 (Box 209)
  - Fle, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 209)
  - Fletcher Trust Company, 1937-1955; (18 folders) (Box 209)
  - Flight Training Course, 1946-1947 (Box 209)
  - Flo, 1937-1951; (14 folders) (Box 209)
  - Flo, 1951-1962; (11 folders) (Box 210)
  - Fo, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 210)
  - Foley, A.L., 1937-1940; (2 folders) (Box 210)
  - The Folio, 1944-1947 (Box 210)
  - Folklore Institute, 1941-1961; (11 folders) (Box 210)
  - Approval of Folklore Degree, 1949 (Box 210)
  - Folklore (Box 210)
  - Football-Old Oaken Bucket Committee (Box 210)
    - Ticket Requests (Box 210)
  - Football, 1937-1946; (50 folders) (Box 211)
  - State Officials, 1945-1946 (Box 211)
  - Football Tickets, 1946-1947; (2 folders) (Box 212)
  - Rose Bowl Corres., 1946-1947 (Box 212)
  - Football, 1947-1948 (Box 212)
  - Miscellaneous Lists, etc., 1947-1948; (5 folders) (Box 212)
  - Football-Complimentaries, 1947-1948 (Box 212)
    - Purdue Game Buffet, 1947-1948 (Box 212)
    - Tickets, 1947-1949; (5 folders) (Box 212)
    - Complimentaries, 1948-1949 (Box 212)
  - Football, 1948-1949 (Box 212)
    - Tickets, 1948-1949; (3 folders) (Box 212)
  - Football, 1949-1950 (Box 213)
    - Tickets, 1949-1950; (6 folders) (Box 213)
    - Miscellaneous, 1950-1951 (Box 213)
    - Luncheon, 1950-1951 (Box 213)
    - Tickets, 1950-1951; (3 folders) (Box 213)
  - Football, 1950-1951 (Box 213)
    - Correspondence, 1950-1951; (5 folders) (Box 213)
    - Miscellaneous, 1951-1952 (Box 213)
    - Tickets (Box 213)
    - File, 1951-1952; (3 folders) (Box 213)
  - Football-File, 1951-1952; (2 folders) (Box 214)
    - Luncheon, 1951-1952 (Box 214)
    - Tickets, 1951-1952; (2 folders) (Box 214)
    - Miscellaneous, 1952-1953 (Box 214)
    - Tickets, (3 folders) (Box 214)
    - File, 1952-1953; (5 folders) (Box 214)
    - General (Box 214)
    - File, 1951 (Box 214)
    - Miscellaneous, 1953-1954 (Box 214)
    - Luncheon, 1953-1954; (2 folders) (Box 214)
    - Tickets, 1953-1954; (2 folders) (Box 214)
    - File, 1953-1954; (5 folders) (Box 214)
    - Thank you letters, 1953-1954 (Box 214)
    - Complimentaries, 1953-1954 (Box 214)
    - Miscellaneous, 1954-1955 (Box 214)
    - Tickets, (2 folders) (Box 214)
  - Football, 1954 (Box 214)
    - Tickets (Box 214)
    - File, 1954-1955; (2 folders) (Box 214)
  - Football-File, 1954-1955; (3 folders) (Box 215)
    - Thank you letters, 1954-1955 (Box 215)
    - Miscellaneous, 1955-1956 (Box 215)
  - Football, 1955 (Box 215)
    - File, 1955-1956; (4 folders) (Box 215)
  - Football, 1956 (Box 215)
    - Tickets, (2 folders) (Box 215)
    - Miscellaneous, 1956-1957 (Box 215)
    - Tickets, 1956-1957; (2 folders) (Box 215)
    - File, 1956-1957; (5 folders) (Box 215)
    - Miscellaneous, 1957-1958 (Box 215)
    - Purdue Game, 1957-1958 (Box 215)
    - Tickets, 1957-1958; (2 folders) (Box 215)
  - Football, 1957-1958; (6 folders) (Box 215)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 215)
    - Purdue Game (Box 215)
    - Tickets (2 folders) (Box 215)
    - Football, 1958; (3 folders) (Box 215)
  - Football, 1958-1959; (10 folders) (Box 216)
    - Purdue Game (Box 216)
    - Tickets, (2 folders) (Box 216)
    - Miscellaneous, 1960-1961 (Box 216)
    - Tickets, 1960-1961 (Box 216)
    - Game, October 29, 1960 (Box 216)
    - Tickets, 1960-1961 (Box 216)
  - Football, 1960-1961; (5 folders) (Box 216)
    - Oregon State Game, 1960-1961 (Box 216)
    - Marquette Game, 1960-1961 (Box 216)
    - Michigan State Game, 1960-1961 (Box 216)
    - Northwestern Game, 1960-1961 (Box 216)
    - Stadium Parking, 1960-1961 (Box 216)
    - Miscellaneous, 1961-1962 (Box 216)
  - Football, 1961-1962; (6 folders) (Box 216)
    - Tickets, 1961-1962; (2 folders) (Box 216)
    - Purdue Game, 1961-1962 (Box 216)
    - Wisconsin, October 7, 1961 (Box 216)
    - Washington State Game, October 21, 1961 (Box 216)
    - Ohio State Game, November 11, 1961 (Box 216)
    - Purdue University Game, November 25, 1961 (Box 216)
  - For, 1937-1940; (3 folders) (Box 216)
  - For, 1940-1962; (21 folders) (Box 217)
  - Ford, Charles Frederick, 1942-1943 (Box 217)
  - Ford Foundation, 1950-1960; (10 folders) (Box 217)
  - Ford Foundation, 1959-1962; (6 folders) (Box 218)
  - Ford Foundation - Polish Exchange, 1958-1959 (Box 218)
  - Foreign Policy Association, 1958-1962; (5 folders) (Box 218)
  - Foreign Scholars, 1941-1942 (Box 218)
  - Foreign Students, 1937-1956; (26 folders) (Box 218)
  - Foreign Students, 1956-1962; (14 folders) (Box 219)
  - Requests for Scholarships for Foreign Students, 1939-1940 (Box 219)
  - Exchange Scholarships for Foreign Students, 1937-1942 (Box 219)
  - Foreign - Visiting Professors, 1958-1959 (Box 219)
  - Foreign Visitors, 1950-1962; (13 folders) (Box 219)
  - Fort Knox, Kentucky, 1939-1940 (Box 219)
  - Fort Wayne-Miscellaneous, 1950-1951 (Box 219)
  - Fort Wayne Civilian Defense, 1944-1945 (Box 219)
  - Fort Wayne Crime and Delinquency Survey made by WPA, 1939-1940 (Box 219)
  - Fort Wayne Extension Center Building, 1939-1942; (4 folders) (Box 219)
  - Fort Wayne Piano Contest, 1938-1939 (Box 219)
  - Fort Wayne Proposed Plans, etc., 1941-1942; (2 folders) (Box 219)
  - Forum folder #2, 1941-1942 (Box 219)
  - Walter B. Foskett, 1950-1951 (Box 219)
  - Fos, 1937-1946; (9 folders) (Box 219)
  - Fos, 1947-1962; (15 folders) (Box 220)
  - Foster, I.O., 1939-1942; (2 folders) (Box 220)
  - Foster, Jeanette Howard, 1948-1950 (Box 220)
  - Foster, John Watson (Box 220)
  - Foundation Information, 1958-1959 (Box 220)
  - Foundation Aid Requests, 1958-1959 (Box 220)
  - Foundations, 1939-1942; (3 folders) (Box 220)
  - Foundation Day Committee, 1938-1941; (3 folders) (Box 220)
  - Foundation Day, 1941-1942; (2 folders) (Box 220)
  - Foundation Day Committee, 1943-1944; (2 folders) (Box 220)
  - Foundation Day, 1947-1950; (3 folders) (Box 220)
  - Foundation Day Deans Honor List, 1949-1950 (Box 220)
  - Founders Day, 1950-1962; (23 folders) (Box 220)
  - Fox, 1947-1955; (8 folders) (Box 220)
  - Fox, Mrs. Joanna Olmstead, 1940-1945; (5 folders) (Box 220)
  - Fr, 1937-1941; (5 folders) (Box 220)
  - Fr, 1942-1962; (20 folders) (Box 221)
  - Fraenkel, Peter (Box 221)
    - 1942-1943 (Box 221)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 221)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 221)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 221)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 221)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 221)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 221)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 221)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 221)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 221)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 221)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 221)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 221)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 221)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 221)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 221)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 221)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 221)
  - Fraenkel, Siegfried, 1945-1949 (Box 221)
  - Fran, 1947-1955; (8 folders) (Box 221)
  - Frank, John Paul (Box 221)
  - Franke, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 221)
  - Franklin, Joseph A., 1937-1952; (15 folders) (Box 221)
  - Franklin, J.A., 1952-1962; (12 folders) (Box 222)
  - Franklin College, 1937-1952; (15 folders) (Box 222)
  - Franzen, Carl G.F., 1938-1948; (5 folders) (Box 222)
  - Fraternities, 1943-1962; (26 folders) (Box 222)
    - Counsellors Committee, 1939-1940 (Box 222)
  - Fre, 1937-1948; (11 folders) (Box 222)
  - Fre, 1948-1962; (14 folders) (Box 223)
  - Freak Letters, 1937-1941; (2 folders) (Box 223)
  - Free, 1948-1955; (7 folders) (Box 223)
  - Free, William T., 1940-1942; (2 folders) (Box 223)
  - Freedom Files, 1948-1949 (Box 223)
  - Freeland, Mr. and Mrs. Hugh, 1941-1948 (Box 223)
  - Fren, 1946-1947 (Box 223)
  - French, J. Wymond, 1937-1952 (Box 223)
  - French Department Applications, 1938-1939 (Box 223)
  - French and Italian, 1943-1959; (2 folders) (Box 223)
  - French Lick-Sheraton Hotel, 1960-1961 (Box 223)
    - Springs Material, 1939-1940 (Box 223)
  - Frenzel, Otto N., 1945-1946 (Box 223)
  - Freshman, 1937-1938 (Box 223)
    - Convocation, 1950-1959; (2 folders) (Box 223)
    - Courses, 1941-1942 (Box 223)
    - Induction in, 1940 (Box 223)
    - Women Living in Dormitories, 1939-1940 (Box 223)
  - Freyre, Gilberto, 1943-1946 (Box 223)
  - Fri, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 223)
  - Fries, 1937-1940; (3 folders) (Box 224)
  - Fro, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 224)
  - Frontiers of Knowledge, 1958-1959 (Box 224)
  - Fu, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 224)
  - Fuchs, Ralph F., 1953-1954 (Box 224)
  - Fuel Responsibilities Schedule, 1948-1949 (Box 224)
  - Fullbright, J.W. (Box 224)
  - Fulbright Award, 1948-1961 (Box 224)
  - Fulbright Information, 1951-1958; (5 folders) (Box 224)
  - Fulbright Information, 1958-1962; (3 folders) (Box 225)
  - Fuleihan, Anis, 1952-1954; (2 folders) (Box 225)
  - Fulwider, Edwin, 1939-1940 (Box 225)
  - Fund Classification, (2 folders) (Box 225)
  - The Fund for Adult Education, 1953-1962; (9 folders) (Box 225)
  - Fund for the Advancement of Education, 1952-1960; (7 folders) (Box 225)
  - Fund for the Advancement of Education, 1960-1962; (2 folders) (Box 226)
  - Fund for the Republic, 1954-1957; (2 folders) (Box 226)
  - Fund-Raising, 1948-1962; (14 folders) (Box 226)
    - Statement, 1944-1949; (7 folders) (Box 226)
  - Fund Statement, 1949-1954; (5 folders) (Box 227)
  - Fund Statement, 1954-1962; (5 folders) (Box 228)
  - Fundamental Education, 1958-1959 (Box 228)
  - Funds, 1941-1962; (6 folders) (Box 228)
  - Furniture, 1960-1962; (2 folders) (Box 228)
  - Future Action, 1940-1942; (2 folders) (Box 228)
  - Future Suggestions, 1944-1945 (Box 228)
  - G, 1937-1944; (7 folders) (Box 228)
  - G, 1944-1962; (19 folders) (Box 229)
  - Gakstatter, Thelma, 1961-1962 (Box 229)
  - Gal, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 229)
  - Gale, Esson M., 1939 (Box 229)
  - Gam, 1937-1955; (10 folders) (Box 229)
  - Gar, 1937-1942; (5 folders) (Box 229)
  - Gar, 1942-1955; (13 folders) (Box 230)
  - Gary Center Survey, 1955-1957 (Box 230)
  - Gar, 1955-1962; (6 folders) (Box 230)
  - Garbage, 1937-1938 (Box 230)
  - Gary Meeting, etc., 1944-1945 (Box 230)
  - Garn, 1937-1940; (3 folders) (Box 230)
  - Garton, Daisy Hinkle, 1940-1948 (Box 230)
  - Garton, Joseph N., 1937-1954 (Box 230)
  - Gas, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 230)
  - Gat, 1948-1955; (7 folders) (Box 230)
  - Gatch, Dean W.D., 1939-1942; (6 folders) (Box 230)
  - Gatch, Dean W.D., 1942-1947; (5 folders) (Box 231)
  - Gates, Ralph, 1944-1949; (5 folders) (Box 231)
  - Gates, Robert E., 1945-1946 (Box 231)
  - Gavit, Dean B.C. (Box 231)
    - General, 1937-1951; (15 folders) (Box 231)
    - Retired Library Committee files (Box 231)
      - June - December 1937 (Box 231a)
      - January - June 1938 (Box 231a)
      - July - December 1938 (Box 231a)
      - January - June 1939 (Box 231a)
      - July - December 1939 (Box 231a)
      - January - June 1940 (Box 231a)
      - July - December 1940 (Box 231a)
      - January - May 1941 (Box 231b)
      - May - October 1941 (Box 231b)
      - 1941-1942 (Box 231b)
  - Gavit-Mann Libel Suit, 1947-1948 (Box 231b)
  - Ge, 1937-1946; (9 folders) (Box 231b)
  - Ge, 1946-1962; (16 folders) (Box 232)
  - Wm. J. Gedney Material (Box 232)
  - Geiger, Beatrice, 1938-1953; (15 folders) (Box 232)
  - Geiger, Dr. Dillon, 1947-1953; (6 folders) (Box 232)
  - Gen, 1948-1954; (6 folders) (Box 232)
  - General Correspondence File, 1953-1954 (Box 232)
  - Gen, 1954-1955 (Box 232)
  - General Education Board, 1938-1945; (6 folders) (Box 232)
  - General Educational Development Examinations, 1946-1947 (Box 232)
  - General Education Cooperative Organization, 1946-1947 (Box 232)
  - General Electric College Bowl, March 21, 1961 (Box 232)
  - General Electric Company, 1959-1962; (5 folders) (Box 232)
  - General Motors, (2 folders) (Box 232)
  - General Motors, 1959-1962; (6 folders) (Box 233)
  - Geo, 1941-1962; (21 folders) (Box 233)
  - Geographical Chart, 1938-1939 (Box 233)
  - Geology and Geography Dept.-Application, 1939-1941 (Box 233)
  - Geology Camp, 1948-1962; (13 folders) (Box 233)
  - George Washington University, Washington D.C., 1943-1952; (2 folders) (Box 233)
  - Ger, 1948-1955; (7 folders) (Box 233)
  - German- Audio-Visual Specialists, 1948-1951 (Box 233)
  - German Department Applications, 1938-1940 (Box 233)
  - German, Germany, etc., 1952-1967; (7 folders) (Box 233)
  - German Headship, 1938-1941 (Box 233)
  - German Women Visit, 1949-1950 (Box 233)
  - German Youth Leaders, 1951-1953 (Box 233)
  - Gi, 1937-1945; (8 folders) (Box 233)
  - Gi, 1945-1962; (17 folders) (Box 234)
  - Gift, 1942-1956; (27 folders) (Box 234)
  - Gifts, 1955-1962; (26 folders) (Box 235)
  - Gifts, 1943-1960; (33 folders) (Box 236)
  - Gifts, 1952-1962; (6 folders) (Box 237)
  - Gift-Steele Estate (Box 237)
  - Gifts to Universities, 1939-1947; (8 folders) (Box 237)
  - Gil, 1937-1948; (11 folders) (Box 237)